import 'package:quiz_app_tutorial/models/question.dart';

List<Question> stl_questions = [
  Question(
    question: 'Q. What is the Standard Template Library?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      ' Set of C++ template classes to provide common programming data structures',
      ' Set of C++ classes',
      ' Set of Template functions used for easy data structures implementation',
      ' Set of Template data structures only',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. How many components STL has?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' 1',
      ' 2',
      ' 3',
      ' 4',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. In how many categories, containers are divided?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' 1',
      ' 2',
      ' 3',
      ' 4',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. Pick the correct statement.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' STL is a generalized library',
      ' Components of STL are parameterized',
      ' STL uses concept of templates classes and functions to achieve generalized implementation',
      ' All of the mentioned',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. What are the containers?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      ' Containers store objects and data',
      ' Containers stores all the algorithms',
      ' Containers contain overloaded functions',
      ' Containers contain set of Iterators',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. How many Sequence Containers are provided by C++?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      ' 2',
      ' 3',
      ' 4',
      ' 5',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. What are the Associative Containers?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      ' Containers that implements data structures which can be accessed sequentially',
      ' Containers that implements sorted data structures for fast search in O(logn)',
      ' Containers that implements unsorted(hashed) data structures for quick search in O(1)',
      ' Containers that implements data structures which can be accessed non-sequentially',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q. What are Unordered Associative Containers?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      ' Containers that implements data structures which can be accessed sequentially',
      ' Containers that implements sorted data structures for fast search in O(logn)',
      ' Containers that implements unsorted data structures for quick search in O(1)',
      ' Containers that implements data structures which can be accessed non-sequentially',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    'Q. What are Iterators?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      ' Iterators are used to iterate over C-like arrays',
      ' Iterators are used to iterate over pointers',
      ' Iterators are used to point memory addresses of STL containers',
      ' Iterators are used to iterate over functions',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    'Q. Which header file is used for Iterators?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
    ' <iterator>',
    ' <algorithm>',
    ' <iter>',
    ' <loopIter>'
    ],
  ),
];
